太搞笑了
That was so funny.
这些笑话是谁写的
Which one of you guys wrote all those funny jokes?
不  陶德  我们插科打诨这里
No, Todd, here at Shenanigags,
都是即兴发挥  现编现演
we make things up on the spot.
来试试吧  给我个建议
Let's try it. Give me a suggestion.
我也不知道
I don't know.
一堆建议
Suggestions?
你的建议就是"建议"
Your suggestion was "Suggestions."
-还打破第四面墙呢  -一点都不好玩
- Way to break the fourth wall. - That wasn't that funny.
我叫布莱恩  你还没把我说服
My name's Bryan and you haven't won me over yet.
-布莱恩  -陶德  在即兴剧中
- Oh, Bryan. - Todd, in improv,
我们向观众寻求建议
we get suggestions from an audience
然后在此基础上搭建场景
then make up scenes based on them.
有一些简单的规则
There are just a few simple rules.
不能问问题  不能拒绝
You don't ask questions. You don't say no.
无论如何
No matter what.